PAULINA WDOWICZ

JUNIOR MANUAL TESTER

+ 48 534 068 439 paulina.wdowicz1@gmail.com https://github.com/PaulinaWdowicz https://linkedin.com/in/paulina-wdowicz

ABOUT ME

Currently, I work as a manual tester for a vehicle and human body simulation desktop program suite (engineering; traffic accident physical simulations). Experienced in cooperation with programming and QA teams to develop and ship bug-free, intuitive software. Participated in 2 program releases and 4 minor patch releases.

Previously, I worked in the field of waste management in the two largest waste management companies in Warsaw. My position required me to be precise, to pay attention to details, to stay in contact with customers and to meet deadlines.

Passionate about video games (Witcher, Gothic), streaming and tabletop RPGs.

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

- LUA
- PYTHON

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- EASY REDMINE
- GIT
- SQL
- JIRA
- MANTIS

COURSES AND TRAININGS

- Fundamentals of Software Testing QATestLab
- Manual Software Testing Basics Udemy
- Jira Beginners Course Project Management Udemy
- Introduction to SQL: Data Management and Querying Khan Academy

LANGUGAES

- ENGLISH intermediate level (B2 certificate)
- RUSSIAN beginner
- POLISH mother language

EXPERIENCE

JUNIOR MANUAL TESTER

06. 2023 - now | CYBID

- Performing functional, regression and exploratory tests to detect defects and ensure compliance with software requirements.
- Documenting test results in Easy Redmine; reporting errors, issues and proposals for new UX/UI features; cooperation with developers.
- Designing, developing and maintaining LUA scripts that automate the testing process using the in-house software wrapper.
- Ticket-based work (Scrum methodology).
- Experienced in remote work (full-time).

ENVIRONMENTAL PROTECTION AND SERVICE SPECIALIST

07.2022 - 06.2023 | "BYŚ" Wojciech Byśkiniewicz

- Preparing and submitting required waste reports and cooperation with institutions in the field of waste management (monthly/annual reports required by Polish law).
- Maintaining contacts and cooperation with clients (by phone, e-mail).

WASTE MANAGEMENT SPECIALIST

01.2019 - 06.2022 | Miejskie Przedsiębiorstwo Oczyszczania Sp.z o.o. w m. st. Warszawie

- Maintaining documentation regarding waste generated by the facility and segregated secondary raw materials.
- Cooperation with external companies in the field of waste management.

MEMBER

01.2015 - 01.2019 | The Warsaw University of Technology Students' Council

EDUCATION

Warsaw University of Technology Faculty of Building Services, Hydro and Environmental Engineering

10.2013 - 09.2019 | Environmental Protection course - Bachelor (BSc.) + Master (MSc.) degree

II agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).